{
    "subject": "resource/This_Boy's_in_Love",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicalBand",
    "object": "resource/The_Presets",
    "human_readable": "This Boy's in Love is associated with The Presets.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5664318203926086,
            "question": "What song is associated with The Presets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48644331097602844,
            "question": "When was 'This Boy's in Love' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4337061047554016,
            "question": "What is the general theme of 'This Boy's in Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3448285758495331,
            "question": "Is 'This Boy's in Love' a popular song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34202221035957336,
            "question": "Can you describe the sound of The Presets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3323352634906769,
            "question": "Who performs the song 'This Boy's in Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3282147943973541,
            "question": "Has 'This Boy's in Love' been used in any movies or TV shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3049415647983551,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with The Presets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29955390095710754,
            "question": "What makes 'This Boy's in Love' a memorable song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2160424143075943,
            "question": "Are there any other songs by The Presets?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=This Boy's in Love is associated with The Presets.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2533_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'This Boy's in Love' a memorable song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2533_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is associated with The Presets?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2533_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'This Boy's in Love' been used in any movies or TV shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2533_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2533_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The documents contain multiple mentions of \"This Boy's in Love\" being associated with various artists, but consistently mention it as a song by Australian electronic duo The Presets. Therefore, the answer to the query should be:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the triple \"This Boy's in Love is associated with The Presets.\" Multiple documents mention that \"This Boy's in Love\" is a song by Australian electronic duo The Presets."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}